欢迎喜欢的朋友加入familyguy百度贴吧共同讨论
或加FG粉丝交流 QQ群 165859780
♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Family Guy 10x08
Cool Hand Peter
酷汉皮特
标题恶搞了《Cool Hand Luke》
一部描述监狱生活的电影
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: zurica wudixny 后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
这么说 Cleveland 你已经彻底看穿了
So, Cleveland, you got to be pretty psyched
尤巴马总统 是吧
about President Ubama, huh?
什么
W-What?
呃 我是说 你记得许多人都是怎么说的 比如
Well, I mean, you remember how a lot of people said, like,
"哦 尤巴马不能胜任那件事"
"Oh, Ubama's not gonna be able to do it,"
可他还真的坚持下去了
but he's-he's hanging in there.
Peter 那是奥巴马
Peter, it's "Obama."
呃 你巴马 我巴马 咱巴马 谁在乎
Eh, You-bama, Me-bama, We-bama, who cares?
不过是个黑人穿了西装 让人有点另眼相看罢了
It's a black guy in a suit, let's just marvel at that.
Cleveland 真是太好了
Gosh, Cleveland, it sure is great
你回到了Clam酒吧 虽然只有短短一周
having you back at The Clam, even if it's just for a week.
(ringtone): ♪ My name is Cleveland Brown ♪
♪ And I am proud to be... ♪
哦 等等 是我的手机响了
Oh, hang on, that's my cell phone.
哇 Peter 你用这首歌做铃声
Aw, Peter, you're using the song!
谢谢你
Thank you.
呃 其实这曲子不咋地
Well, the numbers ain't so good,
所以我们得尽力把它派上用场——啥事 Lois
so we got to do everything we can-- Hello, Lois.
Peter 你又野到哪儿去了
Peter, where the hell are you?
你跟我说过会清理地下室里的那些箱子
You told me you were gonna clean out those boxes in the basement
把它们搬到阁楼上
and put them in the attic.
Lois 那些听着像附加作业啊
Lois, it just sounds like busy work.
busy work指学校为防止学生无所事事而布置的额外作业
就是附加作业
It is busy work.
我就是要让你远离街头混混 远离毒品
I'm trying to keep you off the streets and off drugs.
可我已经把糖果卖完了
I'm selling those candy bars!
喂 喂 喂 喂 你想买些糖果吗
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you want to buy some candy bars
这样我们有钱给自己的棒球队买新队服
so we can get some new uniforms for our baseball team?
你从哪儿弄来的那些糖果
Where'd you get those candy bars?
Peter 我需要你回家
Peter, I need you home.
你也答应过会修好车库里的那个架子
You also promised you'd fix that shelf in the garage.
啊 Lois 我听不清你说话
Oh, Lois, I'm losing you.
喂 喂
Hello? Hello?
喂
Hello?
嗨 Lois
Oh, hey, Lois.
我现在是另一个人了
This is somebody else now.
肯定是串线了
There must've been a cross connection.
我叫Mike 我在别处
My name is Mike, and I'm somewhere else
正要打自己的电话
trying to make my own call.
好的 Mike
Fine, Mike.
请你转告Peter 他回家之后麻烦就大了
You tell Peter he's in trouble when he gets home.
你可以自己告诉他 因为Mike就是Peter
You can tell him yourself, because Mike is Peter!
哎呀妈呀
Oh, my God.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
装得挺像的嘛 Peter
That was very good, Peter.
我知道
I know!
我勒个去
Geez.
我最近的生活就是这样 各种杂七杂八的事
That's all my life is lately, just a bunch of chores.
我真是厌倦了Lois总叫我做这些傻逼事
I'm sick of Lois always making me do stupid stuff.
我懂你所说的 Peter
I know what you're saying, Peter.
Bonnie也总是叫我做
Bonnie's always making me do
那些无法完成的家务活
all these impossible household tasks.
Joe 你得确保
BONNIE: Joe, make sure you get
把地毯上的那些车胎印都清理干净
all the tire tracks out of the carpet.
试着接受这些胎印吧 Bonnie
Learn to live with it, Bonnie!
就是些印记罢了
There are tracks!
是个人就会留下印记
People make tracks!
唉 我也懂你说的
Boy, I hear you, too.
得花很多功夫才能
It's a lot of work just to keep
保持我的单身汉冰箱足够空敞
my single guy fridge sufficiently depressing.
我看看啊
Let's see.
前女友的Yoplait酸奶
Ex-girlfriend's Yoplait.
一个法国牌子的酸奶
两年前的沙士饮料
Root beer from two Julys ago.
找到了 过期的牛奶
Here we go, expired milk.
哎哟喂 Jenny 看看你那会儿多小啊
Oh, my God, Jenny, look how young you look.
你把萌妹子在地窖里关了十几年吗 Giggity
我和你们感同身受啊
I sympathize with y'all.
Donna让我在XM Radio上一天听19个小时的Gayle King
Donna makes me listen to Gayle King on XM Radio 19 hours a day.
Gayle King是自由编辑 奥普拉的好友 XM Radio是一个卫星广播频道
我都想要自杀了
I tried to kill myself by
吞了一把指甲刀 可还是没死成
swallowing a nail clipper, but I passed it.
咱们这究竟是怎么了
What the hell happened to us?
我们也曾经呼风唤雨 为所欲为
We used to be able to do whatever the hell we wanted.
现在再看看我们 正当壮年
Now here we are, in the prime of our lives,
却成了自家老娘们儿的奴隶
and we're slaves to our women.
我明白 唯一让我爽翻的日子
I know. An exciting day for me
就是我看轮椅黄片的日子
is when I watch wheelchair porn.
哎哟 在轮椅上的男女大战
Boy, do the sparks fly on those.
哦 很带劲吗
Oh, is it hot?
不是啦 大部分情景是轮椅撞来撞去
Nah, it's mostly just chairs smashing into each other.
有时候导演还得跑到镜头前
Sometimes the director has to come on camera
把轮椅摆好
just to turn the chairs around.
我们为什么不自己去找点乐子呢
Well, why don't we make our own excitement?
- 你是指什么 - 我不清楚 比如
- What do you mean? - I don't know, like,
也许我们四个可以
maybe the four of us should
做点什么事来宣告我们的自由
do something to reclaim our freedom.
像公路旅行啦 探险啦
Like go on a road trip, find some adventure.
Quagmire 真是个好主意
Quagmire, that's a great idea!
咱们就去公路旅行吧 谁参加
Let's do a road trip! Who's in?
不 不 不
No. No, no.
不 你不行 Seamus
No, n-not you, Seamus.
我擦
SEAMUS: Ah, poo.
你们听好了 女士们
All right, listen up, ladies.
我们有话要说 而且我们不想听你们拒绝
We got something to say and we ain't taking "no" for an answer.
我们要去公路旅行
We are going on a road trip.
不知道我们要去多久
We don't know how long we'll be gone,
而且别指望接到我们报平安的电话
and don't expect a call from us to check in.
这是一次男人的成长之旅
This trip is about men being men.
我们会喝上一堆啤酒再开车上路
We will drive after a couple of beers
而不会因此闯祸犯下全国大案
and not make a big federal case about it.
我们也会不用手掩面就打喷嚏
We're gonna sneeze and not put our hand over (bleep).
你们做什么都阻止不了我们
And there are nothing you can do to stop us!
好吧 我没意见
Yeah, okay with me.
- 行啊 - 好的
- Sure. - Fine.
那太好了
That'll be nice.
咱们有机会享受闺蜜时光了
It'll give us a chance to have some girl time.
哦 那好
Oh. All right, then.
你们几个男的要去哪儿
Where are you boys going?
我们要去新奥尔良
We're going to New Orleans.
美国派对之都
The party capital of America.
"随地大小便"街道之乡
Home of the All-You-Can-Pee Street.
跟你们说件事吧 其实和那里的"珠子"有关
I'll tell you one thing, it's all about the beads down there.
这里指新奥尔良在"忏悔星期二"狂欢节的游行上 向行人抛洒珠串祈福的习俗
我们都知道这是什么事
We all know what's going on here.
如果你不知道，补补AV吧(肛珠)
虽然前面暗示过了 不过我们都知道
It's just implied, but we all know
我这个想法里面究竟是什么
what's going on in this thought bubble.
小孩子们不知道 可我们知道
The kids don't know, but we do.
哎哟 我觉得花钱租这辆车真是值了
Boy, I'm sure getting my money's worth out of this rental car.
哎 听好了 我想到一个问题
Okay, all right, I got one.
你是愿意成为一个流浪汉 有百分之五的几率
Would you rather be a hobo with a five percent chance
继承一个富人的遗产
of getting inherited by a rich guy
还是愿意成为第二次世界大战结束前两年的希特勒
or be Hitler two years before the end of World War II?
假定你已经知道自己会用枪结果性命
'Cause you know you're gonna have to shoot yourself,
可你仍然有两年的时间做希特勒
but you still got two more years as Hitler.
要是选流浪汉 那你 呃
If you're the hobo, do you, uh,
有没有地方睡觉 比如地下通道或者…
have a place to sleep, like an underpass or...?
地方每晚一换
Different every night.
要是选希特勒 我能不能改变
As Hitler, can I change
某些政策 这样也许在战争结束的时候
certain policies so that maybe I'm looked on
我的前景会更有利一些
more favorably at the end of the war?
不 你已经搞砸了一桩大事——死了很多犹太人
No, you already screwed up big-time-- lot of dead Jews.
我是蓝州的流浪汉还是红州的流浪汉
Am I a blue state or a red state hobo?
蓝州指民主党支持者较多的州 红州指共和党支持者较多的州
蓝州的 不过是中西部蓝州
Blue, but Midwestern blue.
哦 哎哟
Oh, boy.
我不那么想 那很冷的
I don't think so, it's cold out there.
我能不能给小胡子换个样式
Am I allowed to alter the mustache?
老兄 为什么你总想着成为希特勒
Dude, why do you keep trying to make Hitler work?
我能不能杀掉其他流浪汉来增加自己继承遗产的几率
Am I allowed to kill other hobos to increase my odds?
你想杀谁就杀谁 你是流浪汉嘛
Kill anyone you like; you're a hobo.
我是一个能走路的流浪汉吗
Am I a walking hobo?
不 Quagmire和Cleveland可以是 你不行
No. Quagmire and Cleveland are, but you're not.
那你是说 我做希特勒也只能是瘫痪的吗
So, wait, I would also be a paralyzed Hitler?
是的
Yeah.
我能成为一个黑人希特勒吗
Would I be a black Hitler?
可以 啊不
Yes. No.
呃 慢着 为什么我只能做一个
Well, wait a minute, now how come I got to be
残废的希特勒 而他却可以做白人希特勒
crippled Hitler and he's still white Hitler?
要是你有这样的疑问 Joe 还是选流浪汉吧
If you got such a problem with it, Joe, just be the hobo!
这个选项没什么意思
This one isn't very fun.
等等 我们这是在哪儿
Wait a minute, where are we?
是啊 看起来这不像高速公路主干道啊
Yeah, this doesn't look like the main highway anymore.
你认为我们搞错方向了吗
You think we made a wrong turn?
希望不是
I hope not.
深南部的这些蛮荒地区
These backwoods parts of the Deep South
深南部指亚拉巴马 佐治亚 路易斯安娜 密西西比等州
迷路可不是闹着玩的
ain't a place you want to get lost in.
哦 不
Oh, no.
别担心 伙计们
Don't worry about it, guys.
我貌似听说过 南方的警长们都非常想
I read nowhere that Southern sheriffs really want
和牛逼哄哄的北方人聊天呢
to be talked down to by big-shot Northerners.
下午好
Afternoon.
警官 怎么着
Officer, what is it?
我们正在上演一场精彩的"城市热点"呢
We are in a tremendous urban rush.
《城市热点》是加拿大一档娱乐脱口秀节目
你们几个家伙不是本地人 对吧
You fellas ain't from around here, are you?
呵呵 警长 我正在学南方口音呢
Hey, Sheriff, I'm trying to learn Southern.
这么说算南方话吗
Is this saying anything?
A-doy-doy-doy-doy!
很抱歉 警长 我们只是想
We're very sorry, Sheriff, and we want to cooperate
最大限度地配合你
to the fullest extent possible.
你是在胁迫我吗
You threatening me?
呃 不 先生
Uh, no, sir.
你叫谁"先生"呢 小子
Who you calling "sir," boy?
我是法定的警长 拿着县里的薪水
I'm an officer of the law, paid by this county.
就不能不注意到你们的车头灯是坏的
And I can't help noticing you got a headlight out.
真的吗 我没看见…
Really? I don't see any...
而且我看到转向灯也坏掉了
And I see that turn signal ain't working neither.
听我说 先生
Now, look, sir,
我也是一名警官
I'm a police officer, too.
我明白这套"程序" 我自己也这么做
I know all the games; I use them myself.
咱们还是有话好好说 你觉得呢
So what do you say we just work something out?
这么说你是个警察 对吧
So, you're a cop, huh?
让我看看你的证件
Let me see your badge.
现在看来你是个老百姓了哈
Looks like you're a civilian now.
我要搜查你们的汽车
I'm gonna have to search your vehicle.
哎哟 看看这儿
Well, lookie here.
看我们在这里面发现了什么
What do we got in this thing?
哦 得了吧 是你栽赃陷害
Oh, come on! You planted that there!
我们有毒品吗
We had drugs?
我的天呐 我干嘛还要醉驾呢
Oh, my God, why am I driving drunk
早知道就嗑药驾车了嘛
when I could've been driving high?
你们几个麻烦大了
You boys are in a lot of trouble.
指挥中心 我是Nichols警长
Dispatch, Sheriff Nichols.
抓到了四个罪犯
Bringing in four perpetrators
怀疑他们携带毒品
under suspicion of drug possession.
特征描述：一个非裔美国人
Descriptions: one African-American,
一个残疾人 一个瘦子 一个帅哥
one crippled, one skinny, one handsome.
好极了
Yes.
你们几个都下车 跟我去警局
You're all coming down to the station with me.
啊 我日
Aw, crap!
别急 别急 伙计们
Hang on, hang on, you guys.
别慌嘛 我知道如何用这家伙的暗语交流
Don't worry. I know how to speak this guy's language.
Keith Urban.
乡村歌手
继续
Go on.
Brett Favre.
橄榄球四分卫 密西西比州人
然后咧
Uh-huh.
我在听着呢
I'm listening.
William H. Macy?
演员兼作家 出生于东南部沿海的佛罗里达
你们几个得吃一段日子的苦头了
You guys are going away for a long time.
看看呀 Cleveland
Look at this, Cleveland.
前面这些人 后面这些人
Front of the bus, back of the bus,
中间这些人——瞧你们做的好事
middle of the bus-- you guys are doing great.
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe this.
用捏造的罪名判我们入狱两周
Two weeks in prison on trumped-up charges.
那场审判完全就是做戏
That trial was a total sham.
是啊 我一看见陪审团 就知道我们有麻烦了
Yeah, I knew we were in trouble the minute I saw the jury.
《恶搞之家》和《辛普森一家》是"宿敌"
还好 至少他们这个陪审团是同行
Well, at least they're a jury of our peers.
我不认为他们会那么想 Peter
I don't think they see it that way, Peter.
你们好 先生们
Hello, gentlemen.
我是典狱长
I am the warden.
你们到这儿来 因为你们是罪犯
You are here because you are criminals.
这儿可不是风景名胜区
This is not a resort.
你们要加倍努力地工作
You will be worked harder than you have ever
比你们悲惨可怜的人生中曾经做过的工作都要更努力
been worked in your miserable, pathetic lives.
也要更努力地玩耍哦 对不
And play harder, right?
我肯定会的
I bet.
向前一步 人渣
Step forward, maggot!
下次就轮到你了
Next time, that'll be you.
为什么这次就不能是他
Well, why wasn't it him this time?!
哦 我好害怕呀
Oh, I'm so scared.
Peter 别搞了
Peter, stop it!
哎 你拿个棒子就了不起啊 是吗
Yeah, you're real big when you got that stick, ain't you?
好吧 我现在不闹了
Okay, I'll stop now.
真是太有意思了 对不对
This is so much fun, isn't it?
是啊
I know.
咱们接下来聊什么
What should we talk about next?
我想到了 咱们来聊女演员吧
I know, let's talk about actresses.
唔 对呀
Ooh, yeah.
我挺喜欢Natalie Portman
I feel like Natalie Portman
觉得她比别人要好得多
thinks she's so much better than everybody.
她就是个屁 她老公也默默无闻
She's nothing, and her husband's a nobody.
为什么Laura Linney总是
Why does Laura Linney always
看起来像刚刚滑过雪的人
look like she's just finished skiing?
我不知道她是谁
I don't know who that is.
真的吗 《如果还有明天》《真爱至上》
Really? The Big C? Love Actually?
从来没听说过她
No, never heard of her.
要是我说Tyler Perry的Laura Linney
Would you know who she was
你应该知道她是谁了吧
if I said Tyler Perry's Laura Linney?
前面是个黑人喜剧演员 应该是讽刺Donna只认识黑人艺人
哦 我喜欢她
Ooh, I love her.
天呐 这里也太热了
Oh, God, it's so hot out here.
是啊 你知道肯定会变热的 只要你听到了
Yeah, you knew it was gonna be hot when you heard
那段孤单的滑棒吉他音和鹰的叫声
that lonesome slide guitar and that hawk's cry.
嗨 这可不是休息时间
Hey! This ain't break time!
回去工作
Get back to work!
♪ 就要见到Liza小姐 ♪
♪ Gonna see Miss Liza ♪
这首歌出自电影《Take the Money and Run》(1969)
♪ 就要前往密西西比 ♪
♪ Gonna go to Mississippi ♪
♪ 就要见到Liza小姐 ♪
♪ Gonna see Miss Liza ♪
♪ 就要前往密西西比 ♪
♪ Gonna go to Mississippi ♪
♪ 就要见到Liza小姐 ♪
♪ Gonna see Miss Liza ♪
♪ 就要前往密西西比 ♪
♪ Gonna go to Mississippi. ♪
哎呀 听听人家黑人在做什么
Man, listen to what the black guys are doing.
我们也要有一首白人的劳动号子
We need a white guy work song.
♪ 好啊 ♪
♪ Hello ♪
♪ 怎么样 ♪
♪ How are you? ♪
♪ 伙计们可安好 ♪
♪ How's the folks? ♪
这是电影《Ziegfeld Follies》中的"The Babbit and the Bromide"
♪ 有啥新鲜事 ♪
♪ What's new? ♪
♪ 我挺好的 ♪ ♪ 那就行 ♪
♪ I'm great ♪ ♪ That's good ♪
♪ 哈哈 ♪
♪ Ha-ha ♪
♪ 真走运 ♪
♪ Knock wood ♪
♪ 是啊 是啊 ♪ ♪ 那就是生活 ♪
♪ Well, well ♪ ♪ That's life ♪
♪ 你知道什么 ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ 老婆怎样 ♪
♪ How's the wife? ♪
♪ 要跑路喽 ♪ ♪ 我的天呐 ♪
♪ Got to run ♪ ♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ 嗒嗒 ♪ ♪ 橄榄油 ♪
♪ Ta-ta ♪ ♪ Olive oil ♪
♪ 再见 ♪
♪ Good-bye. ♪
你是Peter Griffin吗
You Peter Griffin?
是我 谢了
Oh, yeah, thanks.
那是什么玩意儿
What the hell is that?
是喷射飞行器
It's a jet pack.
我会回来救你们的 我保证
I'll come back for you guys, I promise.
你是我的朋友 是我的一切 虽然觉得难以启齿
You're my friend and everything and I feel bad saying this,
可我还是想看到你失败
but I wanted to see you fail.
官方预告：当他们放我们走的时候
Official prediction: when they let us out of here,
我们将不得不经过监狱的纪念品商店
we're gonna have to go through the prison gift shop.
我可不喜欢那样
Oh, I hate doing that.
他们就是那样盘剥你的
That's how they get you.
哎呀 明天能从这里走出去真是太好了
Man, it's gonna feel so good to walk out of here tomorrow.
是啊 其实 时间比我想象的
Yeah, you know, the time actually went by faster
过的要快
than I would have thought.
嗯 你们觉得吗
Uh, you know something?
我们离开了Quahog去探险
We left Quahog to find adventure
摆脱了所有那些烦人的家务事
and get away from all those lame chores at home,
可我得这么说
but I'll tell you this.
现在回想起来 我觉得我们的生活其实没那么糟
Looking back on it now, I don't think our lives are so bad.
是啊 我真的很想Lois和孩子们
Yeah, I sure do miss Lois and the kids.
跟你们说吧
I'll tell you one thing.
我回家之后 要像圆木那样大睡一觉
When I get home, I'm gonna sleep like a log.
嗨 要是你不介意的话 我想插上夜明灯
Hey, I'm gonna plug in the night-light if you don't mind.
其实 你知道吗
Actually, you know what?
我正想跟你说别那么做
I'm gonna go ahead and ask you to not do that.
别再瞎聊了 熄灯了
Knock off that chitchat! It's lights out!
哦 典狱长 因为是我们在这里的最后一夜
Oh, hey, Warden, since it's our last night in here,
我能不能要一杯牛奶
can I have a glass of milk?
我觉得自己会在梦中拉稀屎的
I feel like having dream diarrhea.
最后一晚
Last night?
你以为你们这些人能去哪儿
Where do you think y'all are going?
这上面写着你还有30天的刑期
Says here you got another 30 days on your sentence.
什么 可是法院判决说我们明天就可以回家了啊
What?! But the court said we're supposed to go home tomorrow!
呵呵 在这儿可不是法院说了算 知道吗
Well, the court ain't here, is it?
我的老天 我们该怎么度过
Oh, man, how the hell are we gonna do this
这额外的30天
for another 30 days?
这里就是这么黑
That's the way it goes around here.
一旦你进来了 就别想出去了
Once you come in, you're never allowed to leave.
我的刑期也曾被额外地加了30天
I got my sentence extended 30 days once.
那是45年前的事了
That was 45 years ago.
我的天呐 你们听到了吗
Oh, my God, you hear that?
我们会永远被关在这里的
We're gonna be stuck in here forever!
那我们该怎么办
Oh, God, what are we gonna do?
好吧 我知道我该怎么办
Well, I know what I'm gonna do.
如果我们还要再待一阵子
If we're gonna be here a while,
我要找出这里最肥的一个家伙 海扁他一顿
I'm gonna find the biggest guy here and kick his ass.
等等 我就是啊
Wait a minute. That's me!
哦 不 我还有把刀
Oh, no, I have a knife!
唉 我们该怎么办
Oh, what are we gonna do?!
他们会把我们永远关在这里的
They're gonna keep us locked up here forever!
我们不会永远待在这里的
We're not staying in here forever.
- 我们要离开这里 - 怎么离开
- We're getting out of here. - How?
我们要越狱
We're breaking out.
什么
What?
听着 有时候在生活中
Look, sometimes in life,
你不得不骂一声 "搞毛啊" 然后硬着头皮上
you got to say, "What the hell," and just go for it.
我举个例子 就像我们如何赢得独立战争那样
I mean, that's how we won the Revolutionary War.
上校 英国人无疑是准备渡河了
Colonel, the British are too entrenched across the river.
我已经要求我们的人部署到位了
I've told the men we'll hold our position.
取消命令 告诉士兵们 我们要渡河
Negative. Tell the men, we're going across.
可是Goatbanger上校 我么已经…
But Colonel Goatbanger, we've...
"Goatbanger"意为"操山羊的人"
不 我们必须这么做
No, we need to do this,
因为…呃…因为…战略需要
'cause... for... 'cause of... for strategy.
好的 如果我们要从这里越狱
All right, if we're gonna break out of here,
首先得支开这些警卫
we got to get past these guards.
嗯 我有个主意
Well, I got an idea.
可能做起来不太体面 不过你们耐心候着就是了
It won't be pretty, but bear with me.
哦 不 我从轮椅上摔下来了
Oh, no, I fell out of my wheelchair!
别来帮我
Don't help me!
我要自己来
I need to do this on my own!
你在干什么 Joe 你这不是让我们难堪吗
What are you doing, Joe? You're embarrassing us.
哦 是吗 他们还在往这儿看吗
Oh, really? Are they looking?
没有 实际上他们在努力不往这儿看
No. They're actually going to great lengths to avoid it.
那肯定了 没人愿意
Exactly. No one wants
旁观一个残疾人挣扎着自立的样子
to watch a handicap struggle for independence.
这给我们赢得了至少15分钟转移视线的时间
This will buy us at least 15 minutes of averted gazes.
好的 看我把这出戏演到底
All right, I'm gonna nail this home.
哦 哦 真是丢人啊
Oh! Oh, this is so humiliating.
我一个老爷们儿都要哭出来了
I'm about to be an adult man crying.
我不能走路啊
I can't walk!
究竟为什么我不能走路
Why the hell can't I walk?!
这句话可不是演出来的
This isn't part of the act anymore!
不 不 不 别看
No, no, no, no, don't look.
要是你们有眼神接触 那你就不能不帮忙了
If you make eye contact, you'll have to help.
哎 他们逃跑了
Hey, they're getting away!
放狗
Release the dogs!
哦 我们成功了
Oh, we did it!
你的计谋真管用 Joe
Your plan worked, Joe!
我就跟你们说 这些警卫不会扭头看的
I told you those guards would turn away.
是啊 Joe 太妙了
Yeah, Joe, that was amazing!
这比从一个早产儿那里偷糖果还容易
That was easier than taking candy from a premature baby.
我 呃 我只是来拿这个的
I'm, uh... I'm just gonna take this.
哎 我想到个主意
Hey, I got an idea
肯定好玩的很
for something that's gonna be so (bleep) funny.
好的 Bonnie 去拿来吧
Okay, Bonnie, go get it.
就在衣橱里
It's in the closet.
Brian Brian 到这儿来
Brian! Brian, come out here!
你在干嘛呀
What are you doing?!
我在读书
I'm reading.
什…什…什…
What... what... what...
什么书啊 你在读的
What are you reading?
呃 我刚刚读完了Jonathan Franzen的书
Well, I was just finishing Jonathan Franzen's book.
美国小说和散文作家
嗯 我得说 虽然有可圈点之处
You know, I'll admit it has its moments,
不过整本书完全被过誉了
but it's completely overrated.
我觉得 尽管我不想说几年前
I mean, I'm not saying I wrote something similar to it
我也写过类似的东西 可是我认为…
several years ago, but I am saying...
抓住他
Grab him!
干嘛 干嘛 干嘛 哎 你们要干嘛 喂
What? What? What? What? Hey, what are you doing?! Hey!
- 按住他的爪子 别让他动 - 喂 喂 喂 怎么回事
- Get his paw! Hold still! - Hey! Hey! Hey! What?
- 抓住四肢把他扳倒 - 不 你们要干嘛…
- Push him down onto all fours! - No. What are you do...?
- 我不想穿这个 - 要是他真的太紧张
- I don't want to do this. - If he really starts freaking out,
就把你的小拇指插进他菊花里 - 啊…
put your pinkie in his butt! - Aah!
刺激前列腺
冷静点 冷静点
Calm down! Calm down!
现在该Stewie了
Now Stewie!
好吧 看样子今晚得干掉几个婊子了
All right, I guess this is the night bitches die.
我想知道狱友们今天过得怎么样
I wonder what the chain gang did today.
真希望我们没错过什么精彩的事
I hope we're not missing anything cool.
也许我们该回去了
Maybe we should go back.
伙计们 看啊 有座房子
Hey, guys, look, there's a house.
也许那里能找到些东西
Maybe there's something inside
可以把这些锁链弄开
we can use to get these chains off.
看样子没人在家
It looks like nobody's home.
咦 这些看起来像手铐和锁链的钥匙
Hey, these look like handcuff and shackle keys.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
这些就是手铐和锁链的钥匙
These are handcuff and shackle keys.
经常用当然知道啦
呵 还真是的
Hey, it worked!
哎哟 这屋里有一大堆
You know, there's an awful lot of pictures
警长的照片
of the sheriff in this house.
呃 其实他长得还不错
Well, he's a good-looking man.
我敢说镇上好多人都有他的照片
I'll bet a lot of people in town have pictures of him.
哦 不 是警长回来了
Oh, no! It's the sheriff!
快 藏到衣橱里
Quick, into the closet!
谁在那里面
Who's there?
PETER：是我呀 宝贝
PETER: Just me, sweetie.
哦 我不知道你在家里呢
Oh, I didn't know you were home.
你待在衣橱里做什么
What are you doing in the closet there?
呃…女人的事啦
Um... wife things?
哦 那好吧 那个 我一会再回来
Oh, all right. Well, I'll only be home for a minute.
有几个囚犯从劳改营逃跑了
Some prisoners escaped from the work camp,
我得帮助典狱长找到他们
and I'm helping the warden track 'em down.
哦 也许你应该放他们走
Oh. Well, maybe you should let 'em go.
你知道我不能那么做
You know I can't do that.
你总是在工作
You're always working.
我希望你能多花点时间在家里
I wish you'd spend more time at home.
多花点时间和我在一起
More time with me.
也许你是对的 宝贝
Maybe you're right, honey.
也许我是工作得太投入了
Maybe I do work too much.
就依你了
You know what?
我就放过这些逃犯吧
I'm gonna let those fugitives go.
你是为我才那么做的吗
You'd do that for me?
我愿意为你做任何事情
I'd do anything for you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too!
赶紧出来吧 给我一个吻
Now, come out here and give me a kiss!
Peter 不
Peter, no!
慢着 我是没老婆的呀(⊙﹏⊙b)
Wait minute! I don't have a wife!
往铁路那边跑
Head for the tracks!
哦 不 他们在朝我们开枪
Oh, no! They're shooting at us!
幸好坏人们的枪法都很烂
Good thing bad guys are such terrible shots.
哎哟 这些人还真难打中
Man, these guys are elusive!
快 跳上去
Quick! Hop on!
- 太好了 我们成功了 - 我们做到了
- All right, we did it. - We made it.
真是九死一生啊
That was a close one!
好啦 兄弟们 我们办到了
Well, guys, we made it.
哎哟喂 我觉得自己好像一个星期没吃饭了
Boy, I feel like I haven't eaten in a week.
哎 要是咱们经过了"麦当挠"
Hey, if we pass a McDaniel's
恶搞McDonald's
或者是"汉堡后" 咱们就跳下去吧
or a Burger Queen, let's hop out.
恶搞Burger King
哦 这就对了 我们是在电视上
Oh, that's right, we're on television.
不能插入隐性广告是吧
我想要"烈焰焚情包"
Oh, I'd love a flame-broiled Bopper!
恶搞汉堡王的flame-broiled Whopper
真没劲 我们都明白自己在说什么
So frustrating. We all know what we're talking about.
啊 真是一次大冒险啊
Well, this was quite an adventure.
是啊 回到熟悉的家乡感觉真好
Yeah, it's good to be back in familiar territory.
你们以为自己能跑到哪儿去
Where do y'all think you're going?
你们几个家伙都是县里的逃犯
You boys are fugitives of my county,
我要把你们抓回去
and I'm gonna take you back.
哦 不
Oh, no!
我可不那么认为
I don't think so.
眼下你们得服从我的管辖权 狗屁警长
You're in my jurisdiction now, Sheriff Butt Breath.
哇哦 Joe 你怎么留了这一手
Wow, Joe, how'd you pull that off?
我在"麦当挠"里打了个付费电话
I put in a call from the McDaniel's pay phone
那会儿你们几个正在吃9块装的"麦了鸡"
while you guys were getting that nine-piece chicken McFingers
恶搞麦当劳的Chicken McNuggets
享用着"健怡渴乐"和"法事薯条"
and those Diet Conks and those Fresh Fries.
恶搞Diet Cokes和French Fries
哦 得了吧 他们根本就不卖"法式薯条"
Oh, come on. They-They don't own "French fries!"
你知道吗 你还真有胆量开车在镇上瞎跑
You know, you got some nerve driving around my town
车灯烂了也不管
with a busted headlight.
挡风玻璃也碎了
And a busted windshield.
有外伤也不处理
And an untreated flesh wound.
你曾经和我念过一样的入职誓言 警长
You took an oath just the same as me, Sheriff.
保境安民 勇于奉献
To protect and serve.
不事滋扰 不行不义
Not to harass and douche.
拥有警官证并不意味着
Just 'cause you have a badge doesn't mean
你可以随心所欲地对待别人
you can treat people any way you like.
而且作为一个专业的执法人员
And as a law enforcement professional,
你有义务在道德上比普通人
you have an obligation to be more ethically upstanding
更加正直高尚 而不是连普通人都不如
than the average man, not less.
现在 滚出我的镇子
Now, get the hell out of my town.
做的好 Joe
Nice going, Joe!
嗯 能回到北方来真好
Well, it's great being back in the North
这里的人们都那么文明
where people are civilized.
喂 你们几个人在下面约会吗
Hey, what, are you guys all on a date?
基佬
Gay!
我的天呐 Peter 这真是一段了不起的经历
Oh, my God, Peter, what an experience.
不过最重要的是你安全到家了
But the important thing is you're home safe.
是啊 不过你知道吗 我觉得自己从中学到了什么
Yeah. And you know, I guess I learned something from all this.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们已经做了无数次 所以说咧
We've done this a billion times, so you know what?
我还得把这段语调再说一遍
I'm just gonna do the cadences.
多数剧集结尾的固定模式 不过估计没词可编了 哈哈
中文字幕: zurica 校对: wudixny 注释: zurica wudixny 后期: zurica 压制: zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组